Every other list of favorites, as you can see, the past year, 2024, we can see the standard
extension that may be our year. So this isn't the extension that we're chosen for the year.
So the first one is automate browser apps in your eyes. So we see the application that we allow
us to automate some of the stuff with artificial intelligence. Obviously, it's a popular
thing now, and it's easy to monetize. 100%. You can get very stable income of that. Another one
is momentum. So what is momentum? It can transform in browser into beautiful design tabs.
So we see the special design and we see also the free features and even the paid features,
right? So you can even add some design if you would like to change it from visual way. There is a
volume master. It has been highly rated. It allows you to increase the volume master slider for each
and audio. So if something is very quiet, you wouldn't be able to hear because, for example,
you are using in build speakers in a monitor. Actually, it can be home very handy.
Another one is text placed in place in snippets. It will help you to create smart text
expansions to get more downstream when you work. And as you can see, a billion of keystrokes,
you can insert it easily. And especially if you have to do some repetitive stuff, it's awesome.
To do is, obviously, the application server is popular. So this is the only thing that you can install
for your Chrome. And obviously, this is the to do is application directly from a Chrome with
browser, tasks, and priority, deadlines, and all the stuff. So as you can see, this is today,
you can specify it. There is other as well, tasks related to this application. This is a coupon
board. So coupon boards automatically finds coupon, the save money for your online shopping.
And as you can see, this is 100% free in use. And I think it's the most popular in US. So we see
Walmart may seem in other tools. Still popular. We have a few similar, actually, extensions like that
for Apple. Services like in China, like in Europe, there is a coupon, keep it as well. Similar,
maybe to coupon boards, but it's more like for the price tracking, so be able to see if the price
is all time low. Another one is stylish custom themes for any website. So we'll be able to customize
the website with even the free themes. Immersive translate. So this is as well, some sort of the
extension that we exchange in build translation for the Chrome. As you can see, maybe some people find
it like not very correct. And it offers more identifying the main area concepts. Let me see the
screen. So as you can see, we have other options that we can use. Another one is iStodo. So this is the
3D game that is slide by. And people, obviously, we can try it out ourselves and see if that came
can succeed. And this is the turn of the lights. So the entire patch will be fading too dark. So you
can watch the videos as you were in the cinema. So you can maybe watch it and see how it works.
I will just add it as well. And this is the other note, work clipper. It's just to save some of
your notes. It's similar maybe to do this. It's more focused on tasks, but it was installed.
So we can subscribe to the YouTube, but I will not do it. But as you can see,
I never noticed more focus on clipping, for example, some parts of the website to create our notes.
But both of these things can be done actually in both of these services. The turn of the lights.
And I can now make it appear. This is the dodo game. And let me turn off the lights. So I see
some of the video if I press it now. As you can see, everything is darker. You can focus on the video.
That's great. And another extension of the norm was a game. So if you're up in the game,
as you can see, it's possible here. It's a pixel. I can set up the play. And we can play it.
And it looks really nice. Don't fall off. So you can use it. It looks very nice.
Okay, I cannot see you. I thought I can call it, but the stuff you know, option to monetize,
it's possible to sign up synchronize. There's a possibility to adjust the sounds.
And there are some skins. Maybe some of the skins can be unlocked by finishing maps.
There is a way obviously to monetize, but I think it's just not a big product to be able to
and get some stable income from that.